BAD DAY
What is this place?
Seriously, you sell jokes?
Okay, I can really use a laugh now
So, I was in my garden.......
..then I got a call....
What man, you call that a joke!!?
Yeah, didn't you like it?
No, I didn't. It is not funny!!
It is funny dude, it's a good joke
No, it isn't. If it were a good joke
I would have laughed
Maybe, you didn't get the joke.
Now you are just insulting me,
I've had enough. I want my money back
To get your money back,
give my joke back first
What, you want me to retell that joke?
Yeah
That joke is long and boring
How can anyone recall all the ueseless stuff?
Too bad, that's not my problem
This is just pathetic, all I wanted is a laugh
but, you ruined my day even more. Keep the money